question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
